Stop that! Why are you doing that?
停！你為什麼要這樣？
Stop!
停!
I need to pee!
我要尿尿！
So you have to kill us all?
所以你就要用尖叫把我們殺光？
Come.
過來
No!
不要！
I said "come".
我說”過來”
No. I don't want her to hurt me.
不要，她會打我！
I'm not gonna hurt you!
我才不會打你
Spirit, spirit, out!
邪靈退散！ 邪靈退散！
Let me go!
放開我！
Out! In the name of Jesus!
奉耶穌的名我命邪靈退散！
- Let me go! - Out! Out!
- 放開我！  - 退散！退散！
The height of disrespect!
這也太不尊重人了！
Do you have to throw that at me?
你一定要朝我丟這種東西嘛？
Medicine will not heal her.
藥物無法治療她，
I know prayer does.
但我知道禱告可以
We must find this church today.
我們今天一定要找到這間教堂
I got all my eggs in this car.
我最重要的東西都在車上、
I need to know where I'm going.
我必須清楚知道我們要去哪
Where are you going?
你要去哪？
Answer me!
回答我！
Just give her her medicine and she'll be fine.
只要給她吃點藥她就會好很多的
It's a spirit!
這是邪靈作祟!
I know it.
我知道的
How ya doin'?
你好 有什麼事情嗎?
Yeah, I'm kinda a little lost.
嗯...我有點迷路了…
I'm looking for a church.
我在找一間教堂
A church? Which church you looking for?
教堂？你在找哪一間？
It's not your fault, bless you.
這不是你的錯，願上帝保佑你
Your father never took you home.
你爸爸從未把你接回家
Do it this time for me, my blessing?
就只這一次，就當為了我好不好、寶貝？
Please?
拜託？
Huh?
好嗎？
I said I need to pee.
我說了我要尿尿
Come back.
回來
The church down the road's about two miles.
再兩公里就會看到這條路上的教堂了
You go about two miles back down the road
你先開回到道路上，
and you take a right on a dirt road.
開兩公里後右轉進有一條沒鋪的紅土路
You go about two more miles
然後再開兩公里，
and you'll see the only church we have down here.
就會看到我們這邊唯一一間教堂了
-Alright. Thank you.  - Yes sir.
- 好的，謝謝！- 不會
Are you gonna pee, or what?
你到底尿不尿？
I'm gonna pee on you.
我要尿在你身上
Yeah right.
最好是啦
Where we goin'?
我們要去哪裡？
How many steps do you think it is to get home?
你覺得從這裡要走幾步才會到我們家阿？
You gonna sing?
你等一下是要去唱歌嗎？
Grandma!
奶奶！
# Oh how I love Jesus Oh how I love Jesus #
（歌詞）噢！我深愛耶穌！深愛耶穌
Hallelujah, hallelujah, hallelujah!
讚美主，讚美主，讚美主！
Thank you, Jesus.
謝謝耶穌
In the name of Jesus, Holy Ghost fire
奉耶穌的名   聖靈的火！
Let him go right now.
現在就把邪靈趕走
Let him go! Let him go!
惡靈退散! 惡靈退散!
In the name of Jesus!
奉耶穌的名！
The word of God says strangers...
聖經上說外邦人要投降於我
Strangers shall submit!
外邦人都該順服！
They shall be afraid out of their closed places.
他們都應感到害怕離開他們被關住的地方
Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire! Fire!
火! 火! 火! 火! 火!
Holy Ghost fire! Holy Ghost fire! Right now!
聖靈之火！ 聖靈之火！ 現在！
Fire! Fire! Fire! Holy Ghost Fire!
火! 火! 火!  聖靈之火！
Begin to churn! Begin to churn!
開始翻攪！開始翻攪！
開始翻攪！！開始翻攪！
Every piece of you vomiting.
你會一點一點把它吐出來
In the name of Jesus!
奉耶穌的名！
Listen. Do this for me. Please.
聽著，就當是為了我 好嗎？
But!
但是！
Do this for mama.
為奶奶做一次
Listen, don't you trust me?
聽我說，難道你不相信我嗎？
Is there anybody here that does not know Jesus,
還有沒有人還不認識耶穌，
and wants to know him?
並且想認識他的？
Anybody else?
有嗎？
Don't be shy, if you want God to touch you today.
如果你希望感覺到上帝，不要害羞！
Hallelujah!
哈利路亞！
Anybody else that wants me to pray for them?
那有人希望由我為你禱告的嗎？
Come! Come! Come! Come! Come!
出來！來！來！來！來！
Come on! Come on! Come on!
過來！過來！過來！
Bring that little girl here - she has a bright future.
帶那個女孩子上來！  她有大好前程在等她
Jesus is willing to set you free, right now.
耶穌願意現在就釋放你
Come on! Come on! Come on!
來！來！來！
Bring her here!
把她帶來這邊！
In the name of Jesus, I command every foul spirit
奉耶穌的名，我命一切汙穢的邪靈都離開！
that is causing you to be rebellious,
要這個讓你叛逆的邪靈
to come out of you right now.
從你身體裡出來！
Right now! Right now! In the name of Jesus
現在！現在！奉耶穌的名
I command you to come out!
我命令你離開！
Right now! Come out right now!
就是現在！現在離開！
Come out right now!
現在出來！
In the name of Jesus! Right now!
奉耶穌的名！就是現在！
The fire of God! The fire of God!
上帝之火！上帝之火！
In the name of Jesus come out right now!
奉耶穌的名現在離開！
In the name of Jesus come out of her!
奉耶穌的名現在離開她！
I call you here, demon. Let her go!
我在這裡命令你，惡魔放開她！
Let her go! Let her go!
放開她！放開她！
The fire of God! The fire of God!
上帝之火！上帝之火！
The fire of God!
上帝之火！
Holy Ghost fire! The blood of Jesus!
聖靈之火！耶穌的寶血！
The blood of Jesus!
耶穌的寶血！
Holy Ghost fire! Right now! Come out!
聖靈之火！現在！退散！
Come out! Come out! Come out! Come out!
退散！退散！退散！退散！
In the name of Jesus, come out!
奉耶穌的名，離開！
Right now! Right now! Right now! Right now!
現在！ 現在！現在！ 現在！
Come out!
出來！
Lose her body!
離開她的身體！
Now! Now! Now!
現在！現在！現在！
Hallelujah!
哈利路亞！
Is there anybody here who wants to accept Jesus today?
今天有人想接受耶穌到你的生命裡嗎？
Today might be your day of salvation!
今天是你被拯救的日子！
Today might be your day of delivery!
今天是你被救贖的日子！
Today might be your day of healing!
今天就是你改變的機會！
Come to the altar! Let God touch you!
來到祭壇！讓上帝觸摸你！
Come to the altar! Let God touch you today!
來到祭壇！讓上帝觸摸你
Fire of God! The fire of God!
上帝之火！上帝之火！
Blessing! Blessing!
寶貝！寶貝！
What's that going to do?
你這樣也不會有幫助